字幕制作: 呆呆@CMCT
听着 我不想占用你太多时间
Look, I don't want to take up a ton of your time,
但是我要自杀
but I'm gonna kill myself.
我只是觉得应该通知谁一下
I just thought that someone should know.
我不知道该怎么执行
I don't really know how this works.
我是该从立交桥上跳下去被大卡车迎面撞死
I'm probably gonna jump off an overpass in front of a semi, so...
或者搬家公司的大卡车 不能是公交车
Or a U-Haul maybe, just not a bus.
我可不想丢人现眼
I'm not gonna be a dick and make people watch.
但是我必须得死得壮烈
But it has to be big.
必须轰轰烈烈
It's got to be so big that it just...
死得干脆利落
Done. Kills me. Lights out.
要是我半死不活变成了残废
'Cause if it just maims me, and I'm like...
这对谁都没好处
Well, then how's that good for anyone?
然后我还得找个护士闷死我
Then I got to find a nurse to smother me.
如果都这样了 我怎么能让别人明白我说的是"闷死"
How am I gonna get across smothering if I'm...
我们不必在意细节问题
We don't need to get caught up in the minutiae.
我只是觉得作为一个成年人 你应该知情
I just thought that an adult, so, you, should know.
这个
Wow. This is, uh,
你看 这信息量有点大 娜丁
a lotto take in, Nadine. I...
我 我希望我知道该说点什么
I wish I knew what to say.
其实我正在起草自己的自杀笔记
Well, I was actuallyjust drafting my own suicide note. Just now.
亲爱的诸位
"Dear everybody.
你们有些人知道
"As some of you know,
我在每个上课日的中午 享受着32分钟的安宁
"I have 32 fleeting minutes of happiness per school day during lunch,
"which has been eaten up, again and again,
而最近这段美好时光却一次又一次
被同一个衣着邋遢的学生吞噬了
"by the same especially badly dressed student.
最后我想到了 你猜怎么着
"And I finally thought, 'You know what?
我宁愿活在黑暗的虚无当中
"'I would rather have the dark, empty nothingness.'
我真的很想
"I really would.
听上去
It sounds
放松一下
"relaxing.
在没有我的生活里 祝你们活得开心 混蛋们
"Have a nice life without me, fuckers."
我要是动真格的 你会被炒鱿鱼的
You are so gonna get fired when I actually do it.
哦 不敢确定 但是梦想还是要有的
Well, not for sure, but I can dream.
我从头开始讲吧
Let me start from the beginning.
大概二年级的时候我明白了一个道理
Around second grade, I had a realization.
这个世界上有两种人
There are two types of people in this world.
第一种人浑身散发着自信 天生赢家
The people who radiate confidence and naturally excel at life.
太好了 太好了
Yes! Yes!
另一种人希望 这些人生赢家都被一场大爆炸炸死
And the people who hope all those people die in a big explosion.
打倒他们 孩子
All right, knock 'em dead, kiddo.
我哥哥从一开始 就成了赢家
My brother, Darian, was a winner from day one
有大约一百万个粉丝
and had about a million fans.
拜拜
Bye.
他最忠实的粉丝
His biggest one?
就是我妈妈
My mother.
拜拜 亲爱的
Bye, sweetheart.
哦 你们看
Look, check it out. I won.
好吧 老板娘
Okay, boss-lady.
晚上见
See you tonight.
娜丁
Nadine.
我们不能再这样了
We're not doing this again.
你答应过我的 现在就下车
You promised. Now, get out of the car.
好 真是够了
Well, that's it.
如你们所见 我和我妈妈一点也不像
You could say my mother and I weren't exactly peas in a pod.
唯一能搞定我们俩的就是 我爸爸
And the only one who could handle either of us was Dad.
我讨厌你
I hate you.
爸爸有一个几乎不可能完成的任务
Dad had a nearly impossible task.
就是同时搞定我们俩
Having to manage us both.
现在没事了
All right, now.
我知道小孩子会有点小气
I know kids can be mean.
如果有机会
But if you get a chance,
你就往他们背包里放个屁
fart into their backpacks.
真希望你也是小孩子
I wish you were small.
那样至少能有个人陪我吃午饭
Then I'd at least have one person to have lunch with.
然而 学校里最在意我的人是这三个
Instead, the most attention I got at school was from these three.
没人喜欢你
Nobody likes you.
你好讨厌 你还会得艾滋病
You suck and you're gonna get AIDS.
这边 快跑
Over here. Come on!
我的童年一团糟
My childhood had become a raging dumpster fire,
这种难以容忍的噩梦
and I couldn't take one more second
我一秒钟也忍受不了
of this intolerable, unlivable nightmare of a...
打扰一下
Excuse me.
然后 出人意料地出现了一位天使
And then, out of the clear blue, an angel appeared.
可以麻烦你让一下吗
Can you move, please?
她打扮得就像个小绅士
She was dressed like a small elderly gentleman.
她的气息 闻起来像糖果
And her breath smelled of SweeTARTS.
你想把它放在手上吗
You want to hold him?
别把它压死了
But don't squash him.
你好 小朋友
Hi, guy.
你愿意的话 你可以和我一起当它的妈妈
If you want, you could be his other mom with me.
真的吗
Really?
我要当你的妈妈
I'm gonna be your other mom and take such
好好照顾你
good care of you.
两个小时以后 我就不小心把它闷死在笔盒里了
I accidentally suffocated him two hours later in my pencil box.
但是我终于交到了 我的第一个朋友
But I had finally made my first friend.
我们会把无法大声说出来的事 告诉对方
We told each other things we never thought we'd say out loud.
有一次 我爷爷睡衣的裤裆不小心开了
Once, my grandpa's pajama flap accidentally came open,
我看到了他的小香肠 真的好失望
and I saw his Wiener and got real sad.
我妈妈必须吃药
My mom has to take medicine,
不然她就会很烦 在商场里买很多东西
or she'll get upset and buy too much at the mall.
是真的
It's true.
原来克丽丝塔的生活也不完美
It turned out Krista's life wasn't perfect either.
布丁真好吃
Why, this pudding is delicious!
我现在就走 好吗
I'm walking away.
我算什么 算是你妈？
What am I, your mother?
我就该照顾你？
Am I supposed to babysit you?
但我们有彼此的陪伴
But we got each other through.
玩这个
We could play with this.
我们可以玩企鹅女士 嘻嘻
We could play with Mr. Penguin. Hee-hee.
接下来的几年里
For the next few years,
一切都好
everything was magic.
然后
And then
一场噩梦来临
some extremely fucked-up shit happened.
哦 我的天呐
Oh, my God.
我就知道
I knew it.
只是头发而已啦
It's really just the hair.
没那么难看 你头发长长就好了
It's not that bad. You can just grow it out.
上帝啊 你忍心吗
Are you even up there?
嘿 让开 我要尿尿
Hey, move. I got to pee.
但同时 达里安 却长得更好看了
Darian, meanwhile, just got better looking.
而且这混蛋他自己也知道
And that asshole knew it.
那天晚上 我和爸爸买了几个芝士汉堡
That night, I picked up some cheeseburgers with my dad.
我的生活中有什么好的东西吗
What do I have that's any good?
告诉我 我有么？
Tell me that. What have I ever had?
你有很多
Hey, you have a lot.
你拥有爱 你有我的爱
You have love. You have my love.
很快你就有芝士汉堡了
Very soon you're gonna have cheeseburgers.
哦 你看
Oh, look!
我没告诉你吗 芝士汉堡
Did I not tell you? Cheeseburgers.
- 你想吃薯条吗 - 好
- You want a fry? - Oh, yeah.
嘿 那是比利·乔尔的歌
Whoa, hey. That was Billy Joel.
别把比利·乔尔的歌换掉
You don't turn past Billy Joel.
#I might be as crazy as you say#
#If I'm crazy, then it's true#
#That it's all because of you Mm m...#
#And you wouldn't want me any other way#
#You may be right#
#I may be crazy#
爸爸
Dad?
爸爸 你没事吧
Dad, are you okay?
爸爸
Dad!
#It's too late to fight#
爸爸
Dad?
爸
Dad.
#But you may be right#
我就不告诉你们细节了 免得你们难受
I'm not gonna depress you with the details,
我只想说接下来的几年糟糕透顶
so let's just say the next few years were complete shit.
哦 天呐
on, God.
有一件事除外
Well, except for one part.
我有克丽丝塔
I had Krista.
那是上个星期五的事
This was last Friday.
你看我 我心情很好
Look at me. I was in a good mood.
我喜欢被剧透
I love spoilers.
不
No.
是的 我喜欢 这样的话我就不用花费时间看了
Yes, I do. That means I don't have to watch it.
我只需要知道前因后果 然后继续我的生活
Then I can just know and move on with my life.
我给你个提示
I'll give you a hint.
我就知道 我就知道 他们结婚了 太好了
I knew it! I knew it. They get married, yes!
哦
Whoa!
天呐 少管所把他变得好性感
God, juvy made him so hot.
哦 天呐 有件事我忘记告诉你了
Oh, God, I forgot to tell you something.
他现在在宠物家园上班
He works at Petland now.
我该到那儿去 然后说
I should go in there and be like,
打扰一下 泰国斗鱼在哪儿
"Excuse me, where are the Betta fish?
还有 你可以用你的小弟弟插我吗
"And also, could you put your penis inside me?"
哦 没和你说
Not you. God.
天呐 要是你真的那样做了怎么办
What if you actually did that?
要是你在宠物家园失身了怎么办
What if you actually lost your virginity in a Petland?
我觉得不错
I think it'd be kind of nice.
所有的小热带鱼看着呢 感觉会很超脱
All the little tropical fish watching. It'd be kind of spiritual.
哦 我的天呐 你看看
NADINEI Oh, my God.
我哥哥穿的那件巨丑的衬衣
Could you please look at that stupid shirt my brother's wearing?
你还看得见他的乳头
KRISTA: Oh, you can see his nipples.
他怎么都没意识到 他这样做就是在高喊
How does he not realize that all that does is scream,
我对身材的狂热 堪比女孩子
"I have a body complex worse than a girl's"?
他现在还在疯狂健身吗
How much does he even work out now?
他有强迫症
It's OCD.
你应该去见见他的 他曾经发飙
You should've seen him. He had a conniption
因为我妈妈再也不给他买肌酸了
'cause my mom won't buy him creatine anymore.
因为对肾不好
Since it fucks up your kidneys.
我就说 "我知道 达里安 我知道"
I was like, "I know, Darian. I know.
妈妈期望的是
"What, does Mom expect, you to win
你靠人格魅力赢得别人的喜爱
"people over with your personality?"
嘿 只是提前说一声
Hey. So, just a heads up,
昨天你上课的时候说
but yesterday, when you were giving your leoture, you were like,
"哦 这个那个的 然后北方就退出联盟了"
"Blah, blah, blah, blah, then the North seceded from the Union, "
你当时想说的是南方退出了
you meant to say the South seceded.
你不小心说反了
You accidentally said the exact opposite.
我当时不想举手
I didn't want to raise my hand and be all,
"不好意思 这些孩子容易弄混"
"Excuse me. These kids are pretty confusable."
只是觉得你可能想知道
Just thought maybe you'd want to know.
哦 嘿
Oh, hey. Yeah?
- 你逮到我了 - 是的
- Great catch. - Yeah.
现在 我知道讲课时间太长 而且你有可能想不起来
Now, I know that it was a long lecture, and you probably don't recall,
但是 呃 你有没有这样想过
but, uh, was there any point during it where you thought to yourself,
"天哪 我多想有个充实的生活"
"Gosh, I wonder what it's like to actually have a life"?
没有
No.
没有 我的注意力集中在
No, I was too concentrated on how
你讲课讲错这件事上了
you were effin' the whole thing up, so...
我明白
Well, I understand that,
你要知道 我还没有放弃希望 还没有
but just know that I haven't given up hope. Not yet.
好吧
Okay.
我喜欢你今天这件运动衫
I like your sweatshirt today.
很好看
It's nice.
谢谢
Thank you.
你在哪儿买的
Where'd you get it?
运动 运动衫
The sweater. Sweatshirt.
我不知道
I...
我不记得了
I don't know. I don't remember.
酷力欧
Kewlio.
- 对 - 对
- Yup. - Yeah.
我不知道是从哪儿来的 但是
Don't know where that came from. What?
- 他叫什么名字 - 埃文·金
- What's his name? - Erwin Kim.
我不认识他
I don't know him.
你会爱上他的 他很可爱
Well, you would freaking love him. He's adorable.
你要和他谈恋爱吗
So, you gonna hook up with him?
不 不是那样的
No, not like that.
是那种可怜又可爱的
Like pathetic adorable.
我想用婴儿背带 背着他到处跑
Like I want to carry him around in a BabyBjorn.
哦 太好了
Oh. Oh, good, good, good, good!
碰到你了 我太高兴了
I caught you. I'm so glad. Oh!
你喜欢这条裙子吗
Do you like this dress?
看起来丑吗 我觉得看起来有点不好看
Does it look bad? I just think it looks kind of bad.
有点蓬松 而且我不知道
You know, it's kind of poofy, and I don't know.
我的手臂难看吗
Do my arms look bad?
不
No.
对 你的话听上去很不靠谱
Yeah, you don't sound very believable,
你让我好紧张 娜丁
and you're making me nervous, Nadine.
你的胳膊美得让人窒息
Your upper arms are breathtaking.
你要去哪儿
Where are you going? Well,
哦 就在刚才 布伦特给我打电话
it's last minute, but Brent called me.
那个牙医
The dentist one.
他问我 周末要不要去熊果树林
And he asked if I wanted to go to Manzanita for the weekend,
我想的是 你知道吗
andlthoughL "You know what?
我该偶尔自私一下 所以
"I deserve to be a little selfish once in a while, so..."
是婚配交友网站上的那个人吗
Is that one of the, uh, match.com guys?
是的
Yeah.
你想去多久就去多久
You should go for as long as you want.
真有意思 我星期天回来 好吧
Very funny. I'm gonna be back on Sunday. Okay?
给你个惊喜
Just in time to surprise you.
我试过给达里安打电话了
Oh, I tried to call Darian,
但他现在肯定在学习小组
but he must be in his AP study group.
呃 我可以 我会告诉他的
I'll tell him.
要乖哦
Be good.
- 怎么了 - 权利 权利 权利 权利
- What? Huh? - Dibs. Dibs, dibs, dibs!
你在说什么
What are you even saying?
妈妈要和一个牙医在熊果树林缠绵两天
Oh. Mom's fucking a dentist in Manzanita for two days,
所以我要在家做主的权利
so I call dibs on the house, okay?
呃 拜拜
Ew. Bye!
你那样说话真招人厌
Dude, you are so sick for saying it like that.
妈妈的咪咪在牙医的脸上蹭来蹭去
Mom's boobs are jangling around a dentist's face.
看着吧 戴立安
See it, Darian.
妈妈的乳头全在牙医的脸上
See Mom's titties all up in that dentist's face.
上帝 我爱你
Oh, my God, I love you.
他会喜欢你的一口好牙
I love those teeth in your mouth.
- 这是你的鼻子 - 你拍了我的鼻子
- That's your nose. - You just picked my nose.
- 不会吧 - 赢一个
- No way. Mmm-mmm. - Do a gainer!
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
达里安
Daflan!
你让所有人从泳池里滚出去
You need to get all these people out of the pool.
不好意思 你们所有人都得走
Excuse me, all of you need to leave.
拜拜
Bye-bye!
嘿 没人听你说话
Hey, no one's listening to you.
你说你踢完球才会喝酒
You said you weren't gonna drink until after soooer.
你输了 输了
You failed, failure!
伙计 我没喝酒 是橙汁 天才
Dude, I'm not drinking. It's orange juice, genius.
她喝了多少
How drunk is she?
我只喝了一瓶 好吗
I've had one drink, okay?
现在让你的朋友滚出游泳池
Now, you get your friends out of the pool.
呃 不行
No.
好吧 那我就打电话叫警察
Okay, then. I'm gonna call the cops.
好啦 你被切断通话了 我们上楼去
Okay, yup, you're out off now. We're going upstairs.
等一下 我在给警察打电话
Excuse me, I'm calling the cops.
嘿 你个白痴
Hey, you're retarded.
我还在拨号 你好 是接线员吗
I'm still dialing. Hello, operator?
是的 呃 你能帮帮我吗
Yeah, um, can you please help me?
天哪
Oh, my God.
我的哥哥在骚扰我的私处
My brother's hurting me in my no-no hole!
我怎么这么荒唐
Why am I so grotesque?
你怎么可能喜欢我 你是怎么回事
How do you even like me? What's wrong with you?
别说了
Stop.
我自己都不喜欢我自己
I don't even like me.
昨天我在一封语音邮件里听到我的声音了
I heard my voice in a voice mail yesterday.
我觉得 怎么会有人受得了我的声音
I was like, "How could anyone stand listening to you?"
- 你现在只是喝多了 好吗 - 我讨厌我的脸
- You're just drunk right now, okay? - I hate my face.
我讨厌我说话和嚼口香糖的样子
I hate the way it looks when I talk or when I chew gum.
别让我嚼口香糖好不好
Don't ever let me chew gum, okay?
别让我嚼口香糖
Don't let me chew gum.
我有个很糟糕的想法
And then I had the worst thought.
我要孤独终老了
I got to spend the rest of my life with myself.
我们回你房间
Let's go to your room.
难道明天早上 你不想从自己床上醒来吗
Don't you want to wake up in your bed tomorrow morning?
你不想吗
Don't you want to do that?
你不会想睡在这儿的 来吧 纳丁
You don't want to sleep here. Come on, Nadine.
嘿 这里还有阿司匹林吗
Hey, is there any more aspirin anywhere?
应该有吧 到那边找找
Maybe. Try... Try that thing over there.
- 不用 不用麻烦你
Hey, no, you don't have to.
没事 这样更快
No, it's... It's cool. It'll just go faster, so...
好吧
All right.
发生什么事了
So, what happened? Uh...
有人把巴克斯特放进来了 它在这儿尿尿
Somebody let Baxter in and he pissed.
可以再帮我个小忙吗
Hey, can you do me another quick favor?
可以把纸巾递给我吗
Can you grab me those paper towels?
好 顺便帮我把狗狗的小便清理干净吧
Cool, and just clean up all this dog urine?
对 没错
Yeah, right.
哦 我的天呐 哦 我的天呐
0h, my God! Oh, my God!
怎么回事 你怎么能
What the fuck! Oh, oh! God. Can you...
嘿 出去 滚出我的房间
Just get out. Get out of my room, man!
别看了 出去
Just stop looking, man! Just get out!
我不知道 我不知道 我不
I don't know, I don't know. I don't...
我发誓 我不知道发生了什么
I swear I don't even know what happened.
我甚至不知道是怎么发生的
I don't even know how it happened.
怎么回事
It was...
我不知道
I don't know.
我很抱歉 我很抱歉
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我只是在思考
I'm just... Just thinking.
好吧 待会儿见
Okay, I'll see you later.
娜丁 你不能一句话不说就走
Nadine, you can't just leave without saying anything.
娜丁
Nadine.
你是我最好的朋友 我爱你
Look, you're my best friend and I love you.
这不是你的错
It wasn't your fault.
你让我恶心
You disgust me.
很好
That's nice.
留点儿胡子吧 你个变态
Go grow yourself a wispy mustache, you pervert,
离我的朋友们远点儿 好吗
and stay away from my friends, okay?
你刚刚是不是说朋友"们"
Did you just say "friends" plural?
你的头太大了
Your head is too big for your body.
看起来很可笑 你永远也没办法改变
It makes you look ridiculous, and you'll never be able to fix it.
布鲁纳先生
Mr. Bruner.
昨天晚上我没时间写作业 因为
I didn't have a chance to do the homework last night because...
我不知道你知不知道 我爸爸去世了
Well, I don't know if you know this, but my dad passed away.
我很难专心做任何事
It's just been really hard to do anything.
什么时候去世的
Date of passing?
什么 什么时候 他什么时候去世的
- Sorry'? - When, uh... When did he die?
嗯 2011年
Um, 2011.
嗯 我只会给你一年的时间
Yeah, I have a one-year expiration date
用死去的人当借口
on freebies for the dead and dying.
你是认真的？
Are you serious?
你还有机会的
There'll be other opportunities.
你的祖父母总有一天会去世的
Your grandparents can't stick around forever.
去坐下吧
Have a seat.
好 上课了 来观看年轻的林肯
Okay, mass, the Young Mr. Lincoln.
好好享受
Enjoy-
周末过得怎么样
How was your weekend?
过得不怎么样
It was below average.
耶
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
你周末过得怎么样
How was your weekend?
我
Oh, I, uh...
打了高尔夫球
l golfed.
不过是那种迷你高尔夫
You know, like, mini. Like mini-golf.
就像这样
Like...
我不知道怎么会这样 我会捡起来的
I don't know why I did that. I'll pick that up.
不过 我真打了高尔夫
Um, but, yeah. Yeah.
- 是在蒂姆开心乐园吗 - 是的
- Tim's Fun Park. - Yeah.
我喜欢那个地方
I love that place.
有时间我们可以一起去玩
We should go sometime.
是的 我们
Yeah, we should.
但是是和一群人一起去
But with, like, a group of people.
几个人一起去
Like, with several people.
或者就我们两个人去
Or just us.
- 就 就我们俩吗 - 是啊
- Like, just-just-just us? - Yeah. You know.
- 我想我们 - 嗯 或者几个人一起去
- I think we... - Yeah, or a group.
一群人
Yeah. Yeah. A group.
我觉得那听起来很棒
I think that would be... I think that would be great.
人多才好玩啊
It would be so much more fun, right?
对的
You know. Yeah.
我过会儿去找你们 好吗
Hey, I'm gonna catch up with you guys, all right?
- 好的 - 回见
- All right, man. - See you later.
听着 我只是想说
Look, I just... I want to say that, uh,
你是我妹妹最好的朋友
you're my sister's friend,
那天晚上发生的事 你懂的
and what happened the other night, you know...
- 我知道 没事的 - 只是太奇怪了
- Yes, thank you. Thank you. - So weird.
嗯 那只是
Yeah, it was just...
- 对不起 - 我也很抱歉
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
这都是我的缘故
It was all me, 'cause...
哦 这是 嗯
It was, uh... It was, uh...
不管怎么说
Anyways... Yeah.
没事了 我们还会见面的
Cool. I'll see you...
在家里 或是
At the house or...
- 别的地方 - 好的
- Around. - Cool.
和你在一起很开心
I had a really good time with you.
我也是
Me, too.
对不起 对不起 对不起
KRISTA: I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
等等
One second.
没事
It's cool.
接着说
Continue.
好吧 这么做真的很不好
Okay, that was weird. That was a weird thing to do.
你想让我怎么做 娜丁
What do you want me to do, Nadine?
我想让你考虑下 这对我有多糟
I want you to think about how shitty this is for me.
我知道
I know.
如果我也对你做同样的事呢
What if I did this to you?
如果
What if...
如果我喜欢你爸爸
What if... What if I liked your dad?
如果我给你爸爸打飞机
What if I gave your dad a hand job?
哦 路易斯 你腰带别着手机的样子太性感了
Oh, Louis. Wow, you look so hot with that belt phone of yours.
- 克丽丝塔 你回来早了 - 好了
- Oh, Krista, you're home early! - Okay.
为什么 为什么你会喜欢上他
Why? Why? Why? Why do you even like him?
我不知道
I don't know.
你知道的 你知道
Yes, you do. Yes, you do.
难道女孩子就这样 你和他滚了床单
Is it a girl thing that, like, you hooked up with him, so now
- 你就爱上他了？- 不
- you're emotionally attached? - No.
- 不是 - 你是不是下意识里讨厌我
Are you unconsciously mad at me, maybe,
然后你就这样报复我
and this is like some kind of revenge?
你是不是潜意识里对你自己很不满
Are you unconsciously mad at yourself,
然后这样来惩罚自己
and this is some kind of self-punishment?
如果是这样的话
'Cause if that's what it is, then we can work...
你能别说了吗 我要被你逼疯了
Will you stop talking! Because you're driving me insane!
拜托
Please!
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
他邀请我去一个星期五的聚会
He invited me to a party on Friday.
我想让你和我们一起去
And I want you to come with us.
你和他一起去 然后我像个电灯泡一样
Like you're gonna go with him, and I'm gonna tag along.
我得看看我到时候有没有空
I'm gonna have to see if I'm around.
耶
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming.
什么 我很享受
What? No, no, I'm having a great time.
嘿 听着 你们待会可以在草地上野战啊
Oh, hey. Hey, look, maybe you guys can fuck on the lawn later.
注意素质 娜丁
Please rise above yourself, Nadine.
请你滚蛋 达里安
Please suck several dicks, Darian.
嘿 我想介绍几个人给你认识
Oh, hey. I want you to meet some people.
你好 这是克丽丝塔
What's up? This is Krista.
嗨 我是香侬
I'm Shannon. You were in my chem class last year, right?
是的 很高兴正式认识你
Yes! Yes. Nice to officially meet you.
我的天啊 我喜欢你的装扮 太可爱了
Oh, my God. I love your outfit. It's so cute.
谢谢啦
Oh! Thank you very much.
- 蕾丝看起来很美 - 谢谢你
- I love the lace and the necklace. - Thank you.
你想玩啤酒乒乓吗
Hey, do you want to play, uh, beer pong?
可以啊 我也想去玩一玩
KRISTA: Yes! I would love to play beer pong.
我和这儿很多人都不太熟悉
I don't really know a lot of people here.
没问题 你很快就会熟悉的
That's totally fine. Like, you'll meet people.
这是好玩的破冰游戏
It'll be a great icebreaker.
好的 嗨
Sounds good.
我想和他们一起玩啤酒乒乓
Hi! I think I'm gonna go play beer pong with them.
好了 走吧
Come on!
耶 有新人来了
Yeah! New player!
喝吧 喝吧 喝吧
Drink! Drink! Drink! Drink! Drink! Drink!
好了 不要像个怪胎一样
God, just don't be so weird.
天啊 不要表现的这么尴尬啊
God, why are you so awkward?
天啊 好好享受 放轻松
God. Just have a good time.
放松 好好享受
Just relax. Just relax. Have a good time.
去和别人说说话
Go talk to people.
可以嘛 非常好 很完美 我能做到
Okay. All right, great. Yeah, perfect. I'll do that.
那是两杯
That's two cups!
- 我不知道怎么做到的 -你做到了 那是两杯
- I don't know how I did it! - That's two cups!
我可以坐这儿吗
It's cool if I sit here?
嗯
Yeah.
玩得开心吗
You having fun?
挺开心的
Feeling pretty good.
我非常同意
I respect that.
你是达里安·富兰克林的妹妹吗
Aren't you Darian Franklin's sister?
是啊
Yep.
你看过TBS电视吗
Do you watch TBS ever?
有时候看 有一部老电影
Sometimes. There's this old movie
经常播的
that's always playing on there.
里面有阿诺德·施瓦辛格
It's got Arnold Schwarzenegger
和演过《永远阳光灿烂》的那个矮秃头
and the little bald guy from It's Always Sunny?
耶 他们演的是双胞胎
Yeah, they play twin brothers.
但阿诺德又高又帅
Only Arnold's all tall and buff and hot.
而另一个人又矮又长得很搞笑
Yeah, yeah, and the other guy's like little and funny looking.
- 是的 - 天啊
Yes! God.
- 是叫双胞胎吗 - 是的
- Twins! - Yes!
我爱那部电影 太棒了
I love that movie! Love that movie. It's so good.
你和你哥哥 让我想起了那部电影
You and your brother kind of remind me of that.
天啊
God.
我需要你来接我
I need you to come pick me up.
玩得怎么样
How was it?
可能是人生中最糟糕的一个夜晚了
Uh, it was probably one of the worst nights of my life.
你绝不会相信 我今晚经历了什么
God. You wouldn't believe the night I had.
对不起 我看起来糟透了
Sorry I look like hell.
发生了什么
What happened?
这个牙医
So, the dentist?
我今晚在家喝红酒的时候
I was home tonight, having a relaxing glass of wine,
收到了一封邮件
and I got an email
他妻子发来的
from his wife.
我本来打算给心理医师希尔打电话 但是我想
I was about to call Dr. Hill, hysterical, but then I thought,
不行 莫娜
"No, Mona."
你要自己解决
"You're gonna do this on your own.
自从2011年以来 你自己承担了所有事情
"You've done everything on your own since 2011.
这次你也能自己解决
"You're gonna do this on your own, too."
天啊 我觉得自己真是个失败者
God, I feel like such a loser.
你才不是失败者
You're not a loser.
- 我感觉是 - 你不是失败者 妈妈
- I feel like one. - You're not a loser, Mom.
你非常迷人 也擅长装饰
You're attractive. You're good at decorating.
你的眉毛修得很好看
You're very diligent with your eyebrows.
以后不会听到 "嘿 你今天用牙线剔牙了吗"
Think about if it did work out, "Hey, did you floss today?
牙龈病不容小视哦 莫娜
"You know, gum disease is a silent killer, Mona."
你知道我今晚要去做什么吗
You know what I'm gonna do tonight?
什么
What?
我想回家
I want to go home.
做好发型
Fix my hair.
画个美美的妆 穿上我最漂亮的裙子
Puton a beautiful face of makeup and the best dress I own.
再脱下来 然后去睡觉
Then take it all off and go to sleep.
真有意思
Fun.
嘿 尼克 我不久前给你发了好友申请
"Hey, Nick. I sent you a friend request a while ago.
可能你没有看到
"Maybe you just skipped over it.
或是有时候 出了点故障 Facebook没能发出去
"Or sometimes there's a glitch where Facebook doesn't send the email.
所以我想 我应该
"So, I just thought that I'd
和你说一声
"inform you."
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你真是太可悲了
You are truly pathetic.
你好
Hello.
嘿 我是历史课上的娜丁
Hey, it's Nadine from history.
嗯 你在干什么
Um, what are you doing right now?
哦 嗨 我在
Hi, I'm, uh...
嗯 我在
Hi. I'm just, uh...
- 嗨 你还好吗 - 好啊
- Hey. You all right? - Yeah, I'm good.
我是说 你还好吗
'Cause I'm good. I mean, you good?
你好吗 太好了
You all right? You cool? You all right? Great.
你还好吗 有什么事 抱歉 我总是说个不停
Yeah. What's up? Sorry, I keep...
我是说 你过得开心吗 你还好吗
How are you? Are you good? You all right?
蒂姆主题公园 今晚也会营业
Hey, so Tim's Theme Park's open late tonight.
要去那儿一起玩吗
Do you want to meet there?
他们怎么会取消了聚会呢
So, how come they canceled the party?
哦 我说"取消"的意思是 我离开了
Oh. By "canceled, " I more meant I left. Ah.
我懂了
Gotcha. Yeah.
对了 谢谢你载我过来
Thanks for driving, by the way.
我没有驾照 因为我觉得
I don't have a license 'cause I'm like,
为什么不让别人载呢
"Why not just have people drive you?"
人们总是觉得
People make such a big deal about
所有事都要自己做
being able to do things for themselves.
- 我开玩笑呢 我没通过考试
That was a joke. I failed the test.
你可以接
You can get that.
呃 不用了 没什么事
Uh, no. It's cool.
嘿 看啊 摩天轮没人排队
Um, hey, look, there's no line at the Ferris wheel.
告诉我一些我不知道的事吧 埃文
So, tell me something I don't know about you, Erwin.
我
I, uh...
你的梦想是什么
What are your hopes and dreams?
让我走进你的心灵
Take me on a tour of your psyche.
我不知道 我猜我只是一个普通人 我觉得是
Gee. I don't know. I guess I'm just your average guy, I guess.
但你得在坐摩天轮的这两分钟里
Right, but if you had to expand
多聊一些话呢
for the two minutes that we're on the ride?
好的 呃
Right.
- 你父母是怎样的 - 呃 好的 我爸
What are your parents like? Ch. Well, my dad...
等等 让我先猜一下
Actually, wait, wait, wait. Let's see if I can guess.
- 看看我能否猜中 - 好的 当然
- I want to see if I'm psychic. Okay, here it is. - Sure. Okay.
你妈妈会要求你
Your mom gets on you about your grades
好好学习 并督促你练习乐器
and practicing your instruments.
在市区经营小饭店多年后
She makes a great egg sandwich
她能做一个很美味的鸡蛋三明治
after years of owning a small restaurant downtown.
你的爸爸性格是安静的 冷淡的
Your dad, quiet, gruff.
从来不会真正说 我爱你
Never really says, "I love you." Um...
但他很坚忍 我的意思是 你知道他在乎你
But with his stoic presence, I mean, you know he cares.
我希望刚才的话 没有种族主义
I'm really hoping none of that was racist,
但现在我觉得 满是种族主义
but now I'm thinking all of it was.
没有 一点都没有
No, no. Not racist at all, you know. You're good. Yeah.
- 哇 你在干什么 我的天啊 - 对不起
- Whoa! What are you... Oh, my God. - Whoa, I'm sorry.
是时机不对吗
Was that bad timing?
我觉得这个氛围挺好的
'Cause I thought it was good timing
你在摩天轮上 而且有点失落
'cause you're on a Ferris wheel, you're upset.
我只是想安慰你
Okay. I'm just trying to comfort you.
- 那很奇怪吗 - 我们应该下去了
- That was weird? - We should probably get off.
我也这样觉得
We should get off. Yeah, that was...
嘿 打扰一下 能让我们下去吗 埃文 埃文
Hey! Excuse me, could we be let off? Erwin. Erwin?
我们能停下这个摩天轮吗
Can we please? Can we stop the fucking ride?
能让我们下去吗
Can we just stop it?
对不起 我并不是有意嚷嚷
I'm sorry for... I didn't mean to raise my voice.
我的天 埃文
Oh, my God, Erwin.
等等 等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait! Wait!
什么 好的
Okay. What!
你赢了 那都是你的功劳
You got it! That was all you. I got it.
我们赢了
We got it. We got it.
我的老天爷
Holy crap.
没有人看到
Nobody saw that.
我们太棒了 我们走吧
We're good. We're out of here.
今晚真有意思
This has been a really fun night.
对不起 我之前在摩天轮上有点不知所措了
I'm sorry if I flipped out on you on the Ferris wheel earlier.
不 是我没把握好时间
Oh. No, my timing was just bizarre.
我现在遇到一大堆乱七八糟的事
I'm going through a lot of shit right now.
说来话长
It's a long story.
很抱歉 你得经历的这些事
I'm sorry you're going through stuff.
你是个很棒的人 埃文
You're a really great guy, Erwin.
不 我是说真的
No, I'm serious.
我看着你 就好像看到了
I look at you and I just see this really, really,
一个老人
really old man.
- 老人？- 我是在夸你
- old ? - I'm complimenting you.
我是说 看到一个非常体贴绅士睿智的老人
I just see this very kind, very gentle, very wise old man.
在疗养院里
In a convalescent home.
坐在轮椅上
In a wheelchair.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我
L...
我知道你生气了
I know you're mad at me because you think
因为你认为我丢下你去玩啤酒乒乓了
that I ditched you to play beer pong, and...
我从没有说过 我生气
I never said I was mad.
好的 我知道你生气了
Okay, well, I know that you are, and...
娜丁
Nadine.
你想知道这个周末我观察到了什么吗
Would you like to know an observation that I made this weekend?
好的
Sure.
我的天 香侬 你的装扮太可爱了 我很喜欢
"Oh, my God, Shannon. Your outfit, it's so cute! I love it!"
耶 好的
Yeah, okay.
然后你就把我丢在一边了
And you tossed me aside?
是谁自从二年级就一直陪伴在你身边
The person who's had your back since second grade.
是谁和你患难与共
Who's been with you through everything.
你知道吗 别得意太久
You know what? Fine. Yeah, that's what happened.
如果达里安找到更漂亮的女朋友
Because chances are, those pricks,
而把你甩了
they're not gonna give a shit about you
别人都不会再理你了
when Darian drops your ass for someone hotter.
你什么都不知道 娜丁
You don't know anything, Nadine.
听起来很刺耳 对不起 但这就是真相
Look, it's really shitty to hear. I'm sorry. It's gonna happen.
抱歉了 这不会发生的
No, I'm sorry, it's not gonna happen.
因为你哥哥刚刚要我当他女朋友
Because your brother just asked me
并邀请我去五月的舞会
to be his girlfriend and to prom in May.
- 不可能 - 真的
- No. - Yeah, he did.
他刚才问我了
He just asked me that.
你不能什么想要
You can't. You can't have both.
我或他 选一个
It's me or him. Pick.
不 我不会选的
No, I'm... No, I'm not gonna pick.
我还是他 你想要我还是他
It's me or him. Do you want him?
- 娜丁 - 要么要我？
- Nadine. Nadine... - Or do you want me?
- 这没法选择 - 为什么你不能说选我
- This isn't a choice. - Why can't you just say me?
- 选他还是我 - 我说了不会选的
- Him or me, now! - No, I'm not gonna pick!
你猜怎么着 我们玩完了
You know what? Then we're done.
绝交吧
We're done.
好的
Fine.
娜丁
Nadine.
嘿 快醒醒
Hey, wake up.
你刚做了一个头部手术 成功了
You had a brain operation. It worked.
他们让你变得开心随和了
They made you pleasant and agreeable.
只是美好的愿望而已
Ah, just wishful daydreaming.
下课铃响了 快走吧
Hey, the bell rang. Leave, please.
嗯 你知道吗 别管她了
Mmm-hmm. Yeah, you know what, just ignore her. She's...
我待会儿打给你
I'll call you later.
再见
Bye.
我不想再听你抱怨了
I don't want to hear about it.
自己克服一下
Work it out between yourselves.
几个礼拜后 就到了爸爸过世四周年的忌日了
In a couple weeks, Dad'll be dead four years.
今天我在回来的路上 一直在想这件事
When I was on my way home today, this memory came back to me.
在那个晚上
It was that night,
在那一切发生之后
after everything happened.
我起床去浴室时 看到你
I got up to go to the bathroom, and I saw you
哭得很厉害
crying so hard.
你的枕头都湿透了
I mean, so hard your pillow was just soaked.
我看到后很伤心
That made me so sad.
我回到我的房间 把我自己的枕头给你
I got up and I went in my room. I got my pillow.
把那个湿了的枕头留给了自己
Took the wet one for myself.
我希望你爱我 也那么深
I wish you loved me that much.
笨蛋
Asshole.
不 不
No, no.
嘿 你被那件事弄得头脑不清
Hey, you're so messed up for bringing up that story.
你现在一团糟
You're so messed up!
你知不知道提起那件事
I mean, do you even realize how sick
感觉你好像脑子有病
in the head you are for bringing that up?
我很抱歉 你感到愧疚 因为你只关心自己
Oh, I'm sorry you feel guilty for never oaring about anyone but yourself.
是啊 你说的都对
Oh, yeah. No, that's exactly it.
承认吧 你太自恋了
Face it, you're obsessed with yourself.
天哪
Oh, my God.
你在冰箱上贴成绩单 像个五岁小孩一样
Your report card on the refrigerator, like you're five years old!
嘿 大家快看 大家快看
"Hey, everybody! Hey, everybody, look!
我在大厕所大便了
"I pooped in the big potty!"
天呐 你到底知不知道 爱上别人是什么感觉
God, do you even know what it feels like to love another human being?
嘿 你太能搞笑了
Oh, man, you are so dramatic.
听着 生活有时并不公平 娜丁 醒醒吧
Okay? Hey, life isn't fair sometimes, Nadine, okay? Get over it!
我发誓 我发誓 我要杀了你
I swear to God. I swear to God, I'm gonna clock you!
别碰我
Don't touch me, man.
- 别这么对我说话 - 冷静下来
- Stop saying stuff like that! - Calm down already, man!
停下
Stop it!
你们怎么了
What is the matter with you?
- 我知道原因了 - 不 你不知道
- I know what this is about. - No, you don't.
不 我知道 克丽丝塔和达里安在交往
Yes, I do. Krista and Darian are a thing.
你们以为我不知道 我了如指掌
You guys think I don't know things, but I know things.
- 我走了 - 不 你不能走
- I'm leaving. - No, you're not.
- 你要去哪儿 - 我要去散步放松一下
- Where are you going? - I'm taking a therapeutic walk.
回来
Get back here!
噢 天呐 达里安
Oh, God. Darian!
别担心了
Just don't worry about it.
我能问你一个问题吗
Can I just ask you a question?
有必要把我们家变成战场吗
Is it worth turning the house into a war zone?
我该怎么回答
What am I supposed to say to that?
我只是 在问你问题
I'm just... I'm just asking you the question.
不是我要挑起战争 妈妈
I'm not turning it into a war zone, Mom.
是她 你为什么不和她聊
She is. Why don't you talk to her?
因为她不会听我的 而你会
Because she doesn't listen to me. You do.
你会做出正确的选择的 我相信你
You'll do the right thing. I know you will.
看看你做的饮料
I mean, look at that drink you're making.
你想要一杯吗
You want one?
我居然拥有这么好的孩子
What did I do to make such a perfect kid, huh?
请问猫砂在哪儿
Could you point me in the direction of the cat litter?
大概八点钟方向
Uh... Eight, I think.
你去莱克伍德 对吧
You go to Lakewood, right?
偶尔去
Sometimes.
我曾经见过你
I've seen you around.
只是我们从没说过话
We've just never really talked.
高一
Freshman.
高三
Junior.
我不需要猫砂 我只是
I don't really need the cat litter, I just, um...
我不知道我为什么那么说 我根本就没有猫
I don't even know why I said that. I don't even have a cat.
我只是知道它们经常大便
I just know they shit a bunch, so...
我喜欢你的鞋子
I like your shoes.
我要走了
I got to go.
好吧
Uh... Okay.
往好的方面想
Look on the bright side, you know?
我的意思是 也许他们会结婚
I mean, "Maybe they'll get married.
那样你的朋友 就会成为我们家的一分子
"And then my best friend will be part of my family."
很安慰人 谢谢你
Helpful, thank you.
她不再载你去学校 真的很让我困扰
It really bothers me she's not giving you rides anymore, though.
我得和她谈谈
I'm gonna have to talk to her about that.
不可以
No, you're not!
我不能每天早上都载你上学
I can't drive you every morning.
我会在高速路上耽搁四十分钟
It puts me on the freeway late and adds 40 minutes.
如果你这么做 我会做让你同样痛苦的事情
If you do that, I will do something equally terrible to you.
我会在Facebook上告诉所有人 你拔乳头上的毛
I will tell everyone on Facebook that you pluck your nipples.
怎么样
How about that?
好吧 你想听什么 我就说什么
All right. Look, just tell me what you wanna hear, and l'll say it.
- 妈妈 - 我想让你心情好点
- Mom. - I want to make you feel better.
我该说什么才能安慰你
What can I say to do that?
我不知道
I don't know.
当我心情不好时 我会这么做
Here's what I do when I'm feeling down.
我会非常安静 一动不动
I get very quiet and very still.
然后我会对自己说
And I say to myself,
世界上的每个人都像我一样悲惨而空虚
"Everyone in the world is as miserable and empty as I am.
别人只是更善于伪装
"They're just better at pretending."
试试这种方法吧
Try it sometime.
可能会让你感觉好点
It might bring you some peace.
你们知道埃文·金在哪儿
Hey, do you guys know where Erwin Kim is?
我猜他有时会来这里
I guess he hangs out around here sometimes.
是的 他正在准备SFF的项目
Yeah, he's working on his project for SFF.
SFF是什么
SF what?
学生电影节
The Student Film Festival.
- 是吗 - 是的
- Right. - Yeah.
学生电影节
SFF.
我想和你聊聊作业
Hey, um, I got to talk to you about some homework.
我不需要和你聊作业 我撒谎了
I didn't need to talk to you about homework, I lied.
你喜欢我陪着你吗
You enjoying my company?
你像一群猴子一样活跃啊
You're a barrel of monkeys.
你从没告诉我 你有没有妻子
You never told me if you have a wife.
你应该和我妈妈约会
You should date my mother.
她的上一个男朋友是一个网络变态
Her last boyfriend turned out to be an Internet perv.
她非常脆弱
She's very, very fragile.
"噢 救救我"
Very "Oh, save me."
男人喜欢那样的 是吧
Men like that, right, though?
因为男人都想当英雄
'Cause at the end of the day they all want to be a hero.
每个人都想成为生活中的重要人物
Everyone just wants to feel important in life.
事实是 不论他们多么重要
Thing is, no matter how important they are,
总会出现更重要的人
there's always gonna be someone more important.
人们很计较这件事
People get so uptight about that.
噢 不 他们比我好
"Oh, no! They're better than me."
他们没有意识到 别人是否看重你 根本不重要
It's like, God, they don't realize important doesn't matter.
重要的是自信 一旦有了自信
It's confidence. The most confident person
人就会赢得一切
in the room wins every single time.
是否真的自信
It doesn't matter if it's real.
还是胡言乱语 并不重要
Doesn't matter if they're pulling it straight outta their ass.
人们很蠢 他们分辨不出真假
People are dumb. They don't know the difference.
你知道吗
You know what?
我会继续 我要告诉你
I'm gonna go ahead and I'm gonna tell you
我今天和你吃午饭的真正原因
the real reason I'm having lunch with you today.
我现在没有朋友
You see, I don't really have any friends at the moment.
而且说实话 我没有兴趣交朋友
And to be completely honest with you, I'm not interested at all.
我们这一代人都是大笨蛋
My entire generation is a bunch of mouth-breathers.
如果你把他们的手机拿开一会儿 他们会发狂
They literally have a seizure if you take their phone away for a second.
他们只能用表情符号交流
They can't communicate without emojis.
他们真以为 别人想知道他们在干吗
And they actually think that the world wants to know that they are,
在吃墨西哥玉米薄饼卷 感叹号 笑脸
"Eating a taco, exclamation point, smiley face, smiley face."
好像我们都很在乎
Like we give a fuck.
我是一个怀旧的人
lam an old soul.
我喜欢经典的音乐 经典的电影
I like old music and old movies
认识已久的人
and even old people.
我不能忍的是 我和他们没有任何共同点
Bottom line is I have nothing in common with the people out there,
他们和我也没有
and they have nothing in common with me.
娜丁
Nadine?
麦克斯
Max?
也许
Maybe
没人喜欢你
nobody likes you.
你是个混蛋
You're a dick.
也许没人喜欢你
Maybe nobody likes you, huh?
你总是脾气不好
You know, you're always in a shit mood.
你真是一个垃圾的老师
You're a really shitty teacher.
你做任何事情都不努力
You put zero effort into everything you do here,
你没有任何可以值得骄傲的事情
and there's no way you're proud of that.
看看你 看看 你一事无成
Look at you. Look at, like, you do nothing.
看你的头发
Look at your hair.
你没有发型 因为你根本没有头发 你这个秃顶
You don't do your hair 'cause you don't have any hair. You're bald.
你知道吗 你知道为什么你没有结婚吗
And you know what? You know why you're not married?
因为秃顶的男人很恶心
Because bald men are gross, and they're disgusting
尤其是一年挣4万5的男人
and especially the ones that make $45, 000 a year.
怎么了
What?
我做了23年的老师
I've been doing this 23 years,
你是第一个低估我薪水的人
and you're the first person to ever underestimate my salary.
那让我感觉很好
That made me feel good.
我的意思是 太少了
I mean, that part.
你干什么
What are you doing?
我的饼干分你一半
I'm giving you half my cookie.
为什么
Why?
让你感觉好点
Make you feel better. Jesus.
你知道吗
Guess what?
你是我最喜欢的学生
You're my favorite student.
好点了吗
Does that help?
我真的是你最喜欢的学生
Am I really your favorite student?
我只是觉得我应该那样说
Felt like the right thing to say.
顺便说一句 我不是说你一点头发都没有
I didn't mean like completely bald, by the way.
你的造型也很用心
It's smart what you do there, too.
你知道的
You kind of, you know...
我不知道怎么说 把它弄蓬一点
I don't know. Do you poof it up a little bit?
显得头发更多
Give a little zhuzh?
我很高兴你绕回来 解释清楚
Glad you circled back around and cleaned that up.
确实让我感觉好点了
Certainly made me feel better.
那只狗很棒 但是我们真正比赛的是那只癞蛤蟆
The dog's good, but our real competition is the hypnotoad.
- 不不 - 我是认真的
No, no. Yeah. No, I'm serious.
我一直在练习那些步伐
Practice is so totally boring.
我听说你午饭的时候找过我
Hey, I heard you were looking for me at lunch.
我现在不想说话
Yeah, I can't talk right now.
噢 好吧 我只是 好吧
Oh, okay. I just got... Okay.
- 你好 - 对不起
- Hello? - Sorry.
我刚刚吃了一些药
Um, I just took some medicine.
等药劲来了我再打给你
I'll call you after it kicks in.
等等 怎么了 你生病了吗
Wait, wait, what's wrong? Are you sick?
没有 我很好 我没有生病
No, I'm fine. I'm not... No.
只是一些
Medicine, like, uh,
抗抑郁的药
an antidepressant-whatever.
我爸爸去世之后 他们给我的
They gave them to me when my dad died.
然而我只吃了一个月
I was only on them for like a month, though.
很多人经常都吃这种药
People take them, like, all the time.
很正常
It's totally normal.
这是不是让你突然觉得 我很可悲
Does that make you think I'm pathetic all of the sudden?
噢 没有 我觉得
Oh, no. No. No.
我觉得你现在很好
I think you're perfectly fine.
真的
Seriously.
嘿 你家是不是有游泳池
Hey, do you have a swimming pool?
我可以去游泳吗
- Yeah. - Can I come swim in it?
- 我知道我可以在自己家里游 我只是没办法放松
I know I could swim in mine. I just know I wouldn't relax.
当然可以
Yes.
我有毛巾 一切都准备好了
I got towels. We're good to go.
一切都有准备
We're green. We're good.
- 好的 太棒了 - 我发给你地址
- Okay. Cool. - I'll text you the address.
好的 一会儿见
Yeah, I'll see you in a little bit, then.
好的
Okay.
太棒了
Yeah-yeah-yeah. Yes!
天啊 埃文 我应该对你好点的
Jeez, Erwin, I would've been nicer to you.
嘿 我希望我的浴缸也能这么热
God, lwish my bathtub got this hot.
你为什么不告诉我你很有钱
Why didn't you tell me you were rich?
我以为我说了 我总是想告诉每个人
I thought I did. I always try to tell everyone.
什么
What?
你也没有告诉我 你在准备电影节
Well, you didn't tell me that you were in a film festival, either.
你什么都不告诉我 埃文
You don't tell me anything, Erwin.
也许是因为我根本插不上嘴
Well, maybe it's because I couldn't get a word in.
我真的那么能说吗
Do I really talk that much?
是的
Oh, yeah.
我要潜水了 拜拜
I'm gonna drown myself now. Goodbye.
拜
Bye.
谢谢你让我来游泳
Thanks for letting me come over.
我很高兴你能来
I'm glad you did.
你现在想做爱吗
Do you wanna have sex right now?
好啊
Okay.
我只是在开玩笑
I'm just kidding. I was just...
你知道的 我只是在演电影里的场景
You know that I was just playing out the movie scene.
你看这里的瀑布 多像啊
You ever feel like you have to do that?
我的意思是 来吧
I mean, come on.
瀑布太浪漫了
There's a waterfall. It's all romantic.
当然
Sure. Sure. Yeah. Right.
对不起 我只是
I'm sorry. I just...
随便了
Whatever.
你怎么了 生气了
What, are you mad now? You can't be mad.
你不应该对一个男人说这种事
You don't say that stuff to a man.
噢 一个男人
Oh, "a man, " huh?
埃文 回来 你要干什么
Erwin, come... What are you doing?
你想按一个按钮 然后把我吸进排水管里 是吗
You're gonna press a button that sucks rne into the drain, aren't you?
#Dickhead You're such a dickhead#
天哪
Oh, my God.
#And everybody knows it#
#Everyone but you#
#You're a dickhead#
#I hope you'll soon be dead#
#And this is payback time for what you put me through#
#You're a dickhead#
#Everybody's said#
#I hope you like the song so screw you#
你的电影讲的是什么
So, what's your film about, anyway?
我还在做
Still figuring it out. Uh...
我的绘画老师 让我们一些人加入一个动画片项目
My drawing teacher asked a few of us to enter an animation project.
很棒啊 我不知道你还会画画 画的什么
Oh, that's cool. I didn't know you draw. What kind of stuff?
画的太好了
Look at these. Wow.
天啊 埃文
Damn, Erwin.
这些 大多还没有完成
Yeah, this is mostly unfinished.
信手涂鸦
Just doodling, mostly.
还没有
But not quite where I...
噢 我想我找到我最喜欢的了
Oh, I think I found my favorite.
啊 我父母也喜欢那张
ERWIN: Oh, yeah, my parents love that one, too.
- 真的吗 - 他们不喜欢
- Do they? - No, they don't.
他们很保守 不喜欢
That's just... No, they're very conservative. No. They don't.
哇哦 他们都是你 是吧
Wow. They're both you, right?
是的 我有很多面
Yeah, I'm multifaceted.
激进的自画像
Rad self-portrait.
埃文 你真是天才
Man, Erwin, you're really good.
你周六能不能来
Do you, uh, you know, want to come on Saturday?
看电影
To see the film?
时间定在了一大清早 很不方便 所以
It's early in the morning, super inconvenient, so...
我希望你能答应
I mean, I hope you say yes,
你可以考虑一段时间
but, you know, you can take that and think about it.
现在不用回答
I don't expect an answer, like, right now.
因为可能有点没有礼貌
I mean, 'cause that would be rude.
会有点压力
That's a lot of pressure.
所以 现在别想了
So, just laying it out there.
是的 我想参加
Yeah, I'd love to come.
噢 好的
Oh. Okay.
你父母去吗
Are your parents going?
我可以和他们坐一起
I could just sit with them.
我父母要在韩国待三个月
Well, my parents are in Korea for three months.
- 他们来不了 - 真的吗
- So, they won't make it. - Are you serious?
你自己一个人独享这座大房子三个月
You've had this whole place to yourself for three months?
是
Yay.
好吧 我知道了 这房子太大了
No, I get it. It's... It's a big house.
你会无聊的
You're bored.
你知道你需要什么吗
You know what you need?
你需要被人抢劫 这样你就得自己一个人收拾残局了
You need someone to rob you, so you can reenact Home Alone.
那
That is...
那正是我所需要的 谢谢
That is exactly what I need. Thank you.
真是疯狂
That's crazy.
你太坏了
You're so bad.
我不能出去
I can't get out.
你能不能在这条街再绕一圈
Can you just go around the block once?
我不会再绕一圈 我们到了
I'm not going around the block. We're here.
现在不是合适的时机下车 走吧
Look, it's an inappropriate time. Just go.
我必须八点半去工作 娜丁
I have to be at work at 8:30, Nadine.
我的天
Oh, my God.
你又故技重施了吗
Are we really back to this again?
你一定是在和我开玩笑
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
谢谢你 可以只在这里绕一小圈
Thank you. You could just loop around up here.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
我要去工作了 你和我一起去
I'm going to work. You're coming with me.
我的老板不会高兴我这样做
You know, my boss isn't gonna be happy about it,
你负责和他解释
and you're the one that gets to explain it to him.
你没有什么事做吗
Don't you have something to do?
比如校内作业 或者别的
Schoolwork or something?
- 这个打孔机可以给我吗 - 给我拿过来
- Can I have this hole punch? - Give that to me.
我要你在接下来的八个小时 安静地坐着
I want you to just sit there for the next eight hours
不要碰任何东西 并且不要发出任何噪音
and don't touch anything and don't make any noise.
哑剧可以吗
Can I mime?
你一点也不搞笑
You're not funny.
如果我的丈夫知道我现在的处境
If my husband had any idea what I was gonna have to deal with...
我很高兴你以丈夫的名义提到他
I love how you refer to him as your husband.
他是我的丈夫
He is my husband.
你可以向前看 找一个新老公
You can run off and get a new husband.
他是我的爸爸
What he is, is my dad.
你能偶尔这样说吗
Can't you just say that occasionally? Fine.
我们现在不提他 因为太心痛了
But we're not talking about him right now. 'Cause it's just too upsetting.
而且很艰难很伤心
"It's just too hard and too sad
提到他会让我一阵头疼
"and it gives me a cluster headache."
我知道
I know.
噢 天啊 你没有一点同情心
Oh, my God. You have no compassion.
事实上 我只是无聊
Actually, I'm just bored because I know
因为在你做任何事之前我都知道你要做什么
everything you're gonna do before you do it.
- 你知道个屁 - 你不相信我
Sure you do. Oh, you don't believe me.
对 我不相信
No, I don't.
我现在写下来 你接下来要对我说什么
I'm gonna write down the next thing you're gonna say to me.
我不会和你
I'm not gonna play
玩你那些小把戏 娜丁
your little games, Nadine. Your little games, Nadine.
恭喜
Congratulations.
对吧 你知道吗
All right, you know what?
这句话你猜不到
Here's something you're not gonna guess.
现在的你 会让你爸爸很失望
Your dad would be so disappointed in the way you're turning out.
你拿的是我的钥匙吗
Did you just take my keys?
娜丁
Nadine.
你敢开车
Don't you take that car!
我就报警
I will call the police!
我会报警的
天哪
God.
尼克 我只是要告诉你
"Nick, I'm just gonna say it.
我喜欢你 我喜欢你好几个月了
"I like you. I've liked you for months.
每时每刻都想着你
"I think about you every second.
我不知道 或许我已经爱上你了
"I don't know, maybe I even love you.
你是那么的复杂又单纯
"You're so complicated. But simple.
而我感受到我们之间的张力
"And I just feel this connection between us.
感觉我已经认识你了 而且我想和你在一起
"I feel like I already know you, and I just wanna be with you.
我要给你快感
"I wanna give you head.
要你的唇舌舔过我的乳头
"I want you to put your mouth on my tits.
要和你水乳交融
"I wanna feel you inside me.
我们可以在宠物家园的仓库做
"We can do it in the Petland stockroom.
娜丁
"Nadine."
我的天
Oh, my God.
一看就是个神经病
You sound like a fuckin' psychopath.
这信息不能发
You can't send this.
怎么回事 不
What? No.
天 我的天
Oh, my God.
我的天 不可以 不行 不要
Oh, my God, no way. No, no, no way. No.
该死
Fuck!
天啊
Oh, my God!
该死
Shit.
听着 我也不想占用你太多时间
Look, I don't want to take up a ton of your time,
但是我想自杀
but I'm gonna kill myself.
你复杂又单纯
"You're complicated. And simple.
而我感受到我们之间的张力
"And I just feel this connection between us.
感觉我已经认识你了
"Feelike I already know you."
这挺好的啊 你反应过度了
This is kind of sweet. I mean, I think you're overreacting.
我想要和你在一起 我要给你快感
"I just wanna be with you. I wanna give you head.
我要你的唇舌 舔过我的 乳头
"I want you to put your mouth on my tits.
要和你水乳交融
"I wanna feel you inside me." Mmm.
我们可以在宠物家园的仓库做
"We can do it in the Petland stockroom."
求你说说话
Say something.
说话 天啊 求你说说话 帮帮我
Oh, my God. Say something, please! Help me!
你得注意下断句
You need to watch out for run-on sentences.
你能不能做点什么
But can't you just do something?
你不能做点什么吗
Can't you just do something?
你应该可以做点什么的啊
You've gotta be able to do something.
求你了
Come on.
比如没收他的手机啊
I don't know, maybe confiscate his phone? Um...
他的电脑 他的电脑
Oh, his computer. His computer.
或者你可以拿到他的地址
You can maybe get his address.
如果你能拿到他的地址 并没收他的手机
If you get his address, and you confiscate his phone.
就太棒了 拿到他的地址 把地址给我
Great. Get his address. You give it to me.
我去他家 然后我
I'm gonna go there, and I'm...
娜丁 娜丁
Nadine, Nadine.
第五节课你请假吧 好吗 放松一下
Just take fifth period off, all right? Try to relax.
听听音乐 喝点酸奶
Listen to some music. Have a yogurt.
不要激动 可以吗
Maybe just take it easy. Can you do that?
还有 如果你有任何其他纠结
And, uh, if you have any, you know, complications,
告诉我
let me know.
- 好吗 - 好
- Ok? - Okay.
- 别担心 - 谢谢你
- Don't worry. - Thank you.
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
能给我钱买酸奶吗
Can I have some money for the yogurt?
剩下的钱要还我
I want change.
你要知道
I just want you to know
我这辈子都没有这么丢人过
I've never been more humiliated in my entire life.
我绝对不会
I absolutely cannot...
好了 娜丁 现在我要你接电话
Okay, Nadine, so now I need you to pick up the phone.
我就是 就是不懂你 娜丁 我
I just don't understand you, Nadine. I...
你要是觉得你还可以留着手机 你 做 梦
If you think you're keeping that phone, you are dreaming.
你一回家 我马上收了你的手机
The second you come home, that phone is going.
我受够了 我不会再理解你
I am done. I am done trying to understand you.
拜托
Come on. Please.
上帝啊 求求你救救我
Please, God, help me.
我这又是何苦呢
Why do I even bother?
我这又是
Why do I even...
你从没有给我任何东西
You've never given me one thing.
每次我求你的时候 你都是
Any time I ask you for anything, you're like,
噢 你需要帮助啊 我来帮你
"You need help with something? Let me help you.
逗你玩的啦 我要让你更惨
"I'm just playin'. I'm gonna butt-fuck you some more."
你是谁
Wow
天啊
Oh, my God.
天啊 天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
什么
What?
我去
Holy shit.
我去 天啊 好了 冷静
Holy shit. Oh, my God. Okay. Calm down.
别紧张
Just relax.
听起来
Sounds...
不错
cool.
听起来不错
Sounds cool.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
总比这个混蛋好
How many of those do you bet are this asshole's?
这日子赶紧过 快点毕业吧
Please hurry the hell up and graduate.
失陪一下
Hey, one sec.
跟克丽丝塔说说那次
BOY: Oh, tell Krista about the time when...
什么 等一下 不要急 你说什么
What? Wait. Just slow down. What do you mean?
好了 妈 你冷静点
Okay, Mom, calm down.
我已经尽力助攻了
Man, I do my best to big you up.
我是说我们本来可以全胜的
I'm just saying, we could've won every game.
我 我们得下次再聊了
I'm gonna catch up with you guys later.
- 不是吧 兄弟 - 一言难尽
- Are you kidding, man? - No, it's a long story.
- 再见 - 再见
- All right. - I'll see you.
再见 伙计
See you, man.
- 嘿 出什么事了 - 没事
- Hey. Hey, what happened? - It's fine.
没事才怪
It's not fine.
没事 你玩得很开心 你应该留下
No, you're having fun. You should stay.
我和你一起去
I'll come with you.
- 谢谢 - 没事
- Thanks. - Yeah.
你好可爱
You look cute.
谢谢
Thank you.
你也是
So do you... Yeah.
妈
Mom?
妈妈
Hey, Mom?
不
Oh. No.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我要把这些都捐了
It's going to Goodwill. All of it.
地板上的所有东西 都捐了
Everything that's on the floor, gone!
妈 你先冷静下来吧
Mom, why don't you just calm down, okay?
不 我受够了
No. I'm done putting up with it.
全部的东西
All of this?
好了 嘿
All right. Hey.
你能相信吗
Oh, my God! Can you believe it?
- 没事的 - 这是什么
- It's okay. - What is this?
这是什么鬼东西
What is all this crap?
你消停一下好吗
Just please, please stop for a second.
她的卷发器开着不关
She left her flat iron on.
她是想烧了这栋房子
She wants to burn the goddamn house down!
求你了停下来好吗 - 我要扔了这东西
- Can you stop for a second, please? - This is going.
好了 好了
Okay. All right. All right. All right.
停下来 给我
Stop. Just give it to me. Hey!
把袋子给我
Just give me the bag! Hey!
这屋子里我才是大人 你不是
I am the adult here! Not you.
那你为什么老是打电话给我
Then why do you always call me?
天啊
Oh, my God.
天呐 你说的对 对不起
Oh, my God. You're right. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我没有别人了 只有你
Ijustdonfi have anybody else. You're the only one.
你要去哪里
What are you doing?
我去处理这件事
I'm handling it.
看看这景色 太美了
Look at this view, it's amazing.
你知道接下来要干嘛的啦
Look, you know what to do.
不用我多费唇舌告诉你吧
I'm not gonna be an asshole and tell you.
你知道接下来要干嘛的啦
Look, you know what to do...
我喜欢这首歌
I love this song.
真不错
It's really good.
我不敢相信这是真的
I can't believe this is happening.
我有好多话要跟你说 好多事情要问你
There's so much that I've wanted to tell you and ask you.
我真不敢相信 这是真的
And I just can't believe this is happening.
哇哦 这椅子一直往后倒 对吧
Oh, wow, this just keeps going back, doesn't it?
我来脱
Pull this down.
天哪
Oh, God.
我不知道是不是
I... I don't know if...
是
Yeah. Just...
我来就好
Hold on, I gotta...
我不知道该不该
I don't know if I should...
不 下去 下去
No, get off! Get off! Off!
- 放开我 - 好
- Get off! - Okay! Okay.
搞什么啊
What the hell?
我真的挺喜欢刚刚那首歌 叫什么名字
I, uh... I really liked that song earlier. What was the name of it again?
我不记得
Uh, I don't remember.
那我百度一下好了
I can just Google it.
总之
Anyway,
你要不要去散个步什么的
do you maybe wanna go for a walk or something?
我们可以 去看个电影
We could maybe catch a movie.
或者可以一整晚静静地坐在你的豪华大车里
Or we could sit here silently in your Mercury Marquis all night.
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
什么
What?
你现在还来取笑我的车子
What, now you're making fun of my car?
什么 不是 我就是说的具体了点而已
What? No. I was just being specific.
我不是说这车很烂
I wasn't saying that because it's shitty.
- 行了 - 别 不要
- All right. - No, God, no.
你瞧 我喜欢你的车子
Look, I love your car, okay.
我连车子都没有
I don't even have a car.
我的举止是很奇怪 常常都是这样
I'm just acting weird, and this is just all a lot.
拜托 不要走
And please stop. Please don't leave.
- 见鬼 - 怎么了
- Fuck! - What?
- 我不明白 你到底 - 怎么了
- I don't understand you. What do you... - What?
你到底想怎样
What do you want?
什么意思
What do you mean, what do I want?
你到底想怎样
What do you want!
聊天 想了解你
To talk. To get to know you.
而不是见面还没五秒钟就上床
Not just do it in the first five seconds.
你给我写了篇关于你
You wrote me a novel about how you were dying
有多渴望在宠物家园给我吹箫的信息 你个神经病
to blow me in Petland, you psycho.
我来这可不是要了解你
I'm not here to get to know you.
这太蠢了 太蠢了
This is so stupid. So stupid.
早该听我朋友们的话
Why didn't I listen to my friends?
拜托 拜托
Oh, come on. Come on.
难不成你还要我当坏人吗
Now you're gonna try to make me the bad guy?
是你发信息给我的
You're the one who messaged me.
我希望你开这烂车撞大树
I hope you hit a tree in this piece of shit.
撞成瘫痪大傻逼
I hope you get fucking paralyzed!
走吧 姑娘
Let's go, lady.
你买甜甜圈了吗
Did you get a donut from these people?
没有
No.
搞什么
What the...
为什么你的屋子里有个孩子
Why is that baby in your house?
该死 这小东西是怎么进来的
Oh, shit. How the hell'd that thing get in here?
你好啊
Hello.
这是托比 这是格里尔
This is Toby. And this is Greer.
- 嗨 - 你好吗
- Hi. - How are you?
- 很好 你好吗 - 很好
- Good, how are you doing? - Good.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
你好
Hi, nice...
现在 报你妈妈的电话号码
Now, your mother's number?
谁的脚臭 谁的脚臭
And who's got the stinky feet? Who's got the stinky feet?
我来闻闻 等一下
Let me smell. Hold on.
托比的脚好臭啊
Toby's got the stinky feet.
别盯着了 他都不好意思了
Don't stare. It makes him self-conscious.
你还要吃点什么吗
Can I get you something else?
我要抱宝宝去睡了 再给你拿点冰淇淋吧
Any ice cream or anything before I put the baby down?
不用了 谢谢你
I'm good, thank you.
不用了 我可以管好她的吃喝拉撒
No, no, I can feed and water her from here.
好吧
All right.
好的 来吧 宝贝 轮到我和你玩了
All right. Come on, tiny man. It's you and me, buddy.
小伙子 走吧
Big boy. There you go.
好了
Yeah.
我只想说 我不知道发生了什么事情
Look, I just want to say, I don't know the whole story,
但是都会过去的
but, whatever it is, HWlpass.
没多久前 我也过得很糟糕
I went through a rough time not too long ago, too.
但看看我跟了谁
But look where it led me.
我就是希望之脸
This is the face of hope.
好了 晚安
All right. Good night.
- 我马上就来 - 好
- I'll be in, in a minute. - All right. Good night.
- 晚安 - 说晚安
- Good night. - Say, "Night-night."
说 晚安 爸爸
Good night. Night-night, Daddy.
晚安
Night-night.
我想 是有人来接你
I think that's for you.
走吧
Come on.
不 那不是我妈妈 别开门
No, that's not my mother. Don't open the door.
你们好
Hello there.
你来做什么
What are you doing here?
上车 我们回去
Get in the car. Let's go.
- 不 妈妈要来接我 - 不 她不会来
- No, Mom's picking me up. - No, she's not.
上车
Get in the car.
我不想上车和你们坐一起
VVeH, ldon1feelHke getting in the car with you and her.
你知道我整晚都在做什么吗
Do you know what I've been doing all night?
我另外找车回去
I'll find another ride.
嘿 嘿 上车
Hey. Hey, get in the car.
放手
Stop!
不 你觉得这很好玩吗
No, you think this is fun for me?
- 放开我 - 你以为我愿意来吗
- Let go of me! - You think I like this?
你上哪儿去了
Where were you?
你就不能接一下电话吗
You can't pick up your phone even once?
你不用因为大家都看着
You don't need to pretend to give a shit about me
就假装你很关心我
just because people are watching.
饶了我吧
Oh, give me a break.
面对现实吧
Oh, face it.
你迫不及待要带我回家 然后就成了妈妈的小英雄
You can't wait to take me home so you can be Mom's little hero.
你就靠这小成就过日子
You live for that shit.
别往心里去
Just let it go.
达里安
Darian.
Daflan?
达里安
你说的没错 娜丁
Hey, I just want you to know you're right, Nadine.
- 达里安 我们不用 - 你说的都对
Darian, we don't need to do this... You're right about everything!
我一点都不在乎你
I don't give a shit about you.
我来这儿是为了我自己 我的生活妙不可言
I'm only here for me, and my life is fucking incredible.
我爱死了
I love it.
不对 我爱花一整晚的时间 劝妈妈不要跳楼
No, I love spending another night talking Morn off the ledge.
我爱申请离家近的学校
I love only applying to schools nearby
因为谁知道要是我来不及
because who knows what'll happen in the house
赶回去处理 家里又会发生什么事情
if I'm not around to fix it?
而且我就爱
And I love
这么一个让我觉得
that the one person who makes me feel
能好好喘口气的人
like I could take a fuckin' breath,
要是不毁了你 我就什么都没有了
I can't have without completely destroying you.
所以你是对的
So, you're right.
你都对 硝烟弥漫
You're right. It's a blast.
我赢了
I win.
您能送她回家吗
Hey, can you give her a ride home, please?
谢谢
Thanks.
我不是很擅长做这种事
Look, I'm not very good at this kind of thing. Uh...
但我想我们都知道 这时候该说什么
But I think we both know what needs to be said right now,
那么我就顺理成章地说了
so I'm just gonna come right out and say it.
下车
Get out of the car.
- 再见 - 下周一见
- Bye. - See you Monday.
我 我只是想跟你说
Look, I just wanted to say that
我很抱歉 我今晚很过分
I'm sorry for being a bitch tonight.
还有 过去几个星期也很过分
For the past couple weeks.
还有 过去的十七年也是
And the past 17 years before that.
我知道你也并不好过
I know this isn't any easier for you.
我知道的
I know that.
但我想 那个疯狂的我认为
I think some deranged part of me likes thinking
只有我自己是真的有问题
I'm the only one with real problems.
那样我才是独特的
Like that makes me special.
你知道 从我们小的时候开始
You know, ever since we were little,
我就一直觉得
I would get this feeling like...
我的灵魂飘在空中 俯视着我自己
Like I'm floating outside of my body, looking down on myself.
而且我讨厌我所看到的
And I hate what I see.
我的言行举止 我说话的方式
How I'm acting, the way I sound.
而且我不知道 要怎么改变
And I don't know how to change it.
我好害怕
And I'm so scared
好怕一辈子都会这样
that that feeling is never gonna go away.
对不起
I'm sorry.
真的
Really.
晚安
Good night.
嘿 娜丁
Hey, Nadine.
- 晚安 - 晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
你起得挺早的
You're up early.
是啊 我 我有事要做
Uh, yeah. I, um, I got... I got a thing to go to.
是嘛
Yeah.
玩得开心点
have a good day.
你们也是
You as well.
玩得开心点 你们俩
Have a good day, both of you.
好好玩
Have a great day.
谢谢
Thank you.
等会儿 我能给你打电话吗
Can I call you later?
好啊
Okay.
感觉不错啊
That was good.
- 真的吗 - 真的很好
- Right? - That was so good.
我好想她
I miss her.
娜丁
Nadine?
请坐好 放轻松 好好欣赏电影
Sit back, relax, and get ready to enjoy the films.
请关机
Turn off your cell phone, please.
不好意思 谢谢
Can I squeeze in? Thanks.
抱歉 抱歉
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
真的很棒 对吧 让我们接着欣赏下一部电影
Really somethin', wasn't it? Let's keep things going.
我们的下一部入选电影 女士们先生们 是来自 埃文·金
Our next entry, ladies and gentlemen, comes from Erwin Kim of...
谢谢 来自莱克伍德高中的埃文·金 金先生 你想要
Thank you. Of Lakewood High- Mr. Kim, would you like to come out
出来跟观众们介绍下你的电影吗
and say a few words about your film?
掌声欢迎
Come on.
大家好 谢谢各位来看电影
Hello. Thank you for coming. Um...
希望你们喜欢这部 呃
Hope you enjoy this, uh...
我的 呃
My, uh...
请您拿着 谢谢
You can just take this. Thanks. Thank you.
好的 接下来让我们欣赏
Uh, okay. Well, here it is.
金先生的电影
Mr. Kim's film.
很久以前有个星球叫做 没土星
NARRATOR: Once upon a time on a planet called Not Saturn
在外星高中
at Alien Planet High School...
看啊 看啊
Watch out! Watch out! Watch out! Watch out!
有一个外星少年 为情所困
there was an alien adolescent who was struck by love.
太迟了
Too late!
泳池聚会
Pool party!
埃文
Erwin.
真的
That...
- 我是说 - 没那么夸张吧
- Well, I mean... - I wouldn't go that far.
- 还好吧 - 真的很棒
- It was all right. - It was amazing. Really.
谢谢
Oh, thanks!
还有 我明白电影的意思
And I got the message, all right? I know...
我知道女主角就是我
I know she's me.
但我已经知道你有多棒了
But I already figured out how great you are.
你真的太棒了
You're so fucking great.
你像是我认识的最好的人
You're like the best person I know.
怎么了 有什么不对吗
What? What's wrong?
那部电影讲的不是你
Um, the film wasn't about you.
天呐
Oh, God.
糟糕
Shoot
我想可能是因为发型啦
Sorry, I thought maybe because the hair
还有那双很酷的鞋子
and, Hke, the cool shoes that...
我居然是那种自以为是的人
Wow. I'm one of those people that thinks everything is about them.
我逗你玩的
I'm just messing with you.
对 我逗你玩的 是个圈套
Yeah, I'm just messing with you. I set that up.
- 你个笨蛋 - 是啊
- You shithead. - Yes.
感觉太棒了 你终于紧张了一次
Felt pretty good. You... You being nervous for once.
我就这么站着 闻着我的花儿
And I'm just over here, like, just sniff in' my flowers.
我好讨厌你
I hate you so much.
你有空逛逛吗
You free to hang?
是的 当然有空 我的档期都给你
Yeah, I am. Cleared my whole schedule for you.
很好 来吧
Oh, good. Come on.
来吧 跟大家打声招呼
Say hi to some people.
伙计 真的太棒了 干得好
Dude, you did such a good job.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
伙计们 这是娜丁
Guys, this is Nadine.
大家好
Hi. How's it going?
挺好的 你好吗
Good, how are you?
我很好 电影太棒了
I'm good. Thanks. That was so good.
我难以忘怀 真不可思议
I just can't get over it. It was amazing.